Felix Ramirez

(208) 329 5925 📞

felixr91@gmail.com

github.com/Felixr91 (7)

Full stack web developer, and former student from Boise CodeWorks' Immersive Full Stack Program, with experience building web applications utilizing RESTful architecture. Quick learner, able to adapt to changes in software technology and programming languages.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Time Student / Boise CodeWorks

October 2018 - January 2018, Boise, ID

- Worked individually and in teams to build full stack web applications.

ESL Teacher / Jungchul Language School September 2017 - September 2018, South Korea

- Taught ESL to Kinder, Elementary, and Middle School students.

Special Education Teacher / Pelham Lab High School

June 2015 - July 2017, Bronx, NY

- Taught Biology in Special and General Education classroom settings.

Board Operator / Sirus XM Satellite Radio

June 2015 - July 2017, Bronx, NY

- Aired Nationally syndicated Sports broadcasts from the NFL, MLB, NHL, and NBA.

EDUCATION

Masters In Education / Hunter College

June 2015 - June 2017, New York, NY

- Degree in Adolescent Special Education.

Bachelor's Degree / SUNY New Paltz

June 2006 - June 2010, New Paltz, NY

- Degree in Radio and Television Production.

SKILLS

Vue C# Git

Node **CSS** Scrum

Bootstrap MongoDB Javascript

DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

FreePhonics.org

A website of Phonics PowerPoints.

www.freephonics.org

Inspire

A desktop dashboard utilizing AXIOS to make HTTP requests to several restful APIs.

https://felixr91.github.io/inspire/

Holla

A scheduling task manager for agile development teams. MongoDB for database architecture.

https://hollakanban.herokuapp.com/#/login

Battle Cardz

A card game utilizing Vue.js and a game logic API. https://felixr91.github.io/battle-cardz/#/

Flip

A PWA application where users can create, edit, and share mobile flashcards.

https://flipflashcards.herokuapp.com/#/